For those that forgot the roots of country music
this is rebel radio.
Hey, Jesco
I've been listening  to your radio station.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You sound like your fucked up on moonshine.
What are you drinking in there?
Well, tonight, white whiskey
It's not working here no more
You got to get to corn before the corn gets to cry
or weeds don't grow.
This is outlaw, hillbillies will rock your shit
Get your finger off my trigger cause it's hurry
It might blow him kill both of us baby
Yeah.
For those who think  country is gone soft.
Rebel Radio.
This fall you bees out there making that honey
If you're that sweet enough you can fly this way, honey
And you give us some your time to get in here and get your work done
and keep me covered i smoked one
which is a cigarets legal.
Y'all are having a good  time out here, man.
How y'all doing out there?
I'm pretty fucked up here, there in this studio.
And I got one good one going on, man.
We've been partying all day right here.
I ain't nobody  gonna fuck with the rebel radio
Cause I'll back up all these legends and country heroes
Because country music  should fight the establishment,
not become it.
This is rebel radio
My daddy told me
when I was a young boy.
He said jesse if you're gonna get a buzz and get fucked up
and get ripped out of the frame
It's best to do at home.
That way you can save your money
and get to do it tomorrow again.
But if you go to jail,
you're going to spend that money  you get out on.
Then are you gonna have a hangover and broke for not listening to your daddy?
Mm hmm.
Country music
from before country turned into twangy pop sung by frat boys.
This is rebel radio
Have you ever huffed airplane glue?
seem like it take you higher and higher test
That would be a contest between them, too
one's got wings and one don't.
and the one don't have wings say hi all time
no one's got wing crashes
Cause it run out of gas.
That shit of fry you bring when the bag dries on your face, you pass out it man you're a goner
but the high tests keep you walking taller.
Well the white liquor is the best cause it's first
but if it's over 180, it's ....
just better than all the rest of the regular liquor
And it's good whiskey,
and it's guaranteed to kick butt
that trees you gotta put juice with it
we put grape juice with it called purple jesus
And just because you play a guitar
don't mean you got to be a sequin  where and said.
Rebel radio.
This is a radio station  for people like to party
and build bomb farms like myself.
And I  will give you Jesco's  recipe for a good party.
what you do:
starts burning some old furniture you don't have no use for is just dirting up your yard
and put it on air
And the fire will last all night long
you'll get a better buzz instead of going out on the road
you got a taller together, man
you just start drinking and start rocking and have a ball
Because corporate country ain't country.
It's car break.
Rebel radio.
And this is the stories  I want to really tell you.
You people might believe in UFOs
and you might not.
But seeing is believing.
I had a barbecue cookout with my friends
one went to the shit house
and I was on a break smoking me a good doobie
which was good as kicking skunk
And I was drinking some that clear water, man.
and i saw handing were two people here and it was six steaks on the grill
I got the thinking
No wonder the mother f**kers up are shooting
heat all six of them left me one at eight fur
Well, he comes back, I swore
and I pray my hand to God
I did not steal  the rest of those steaks.
Asked him why you had to go shit for.
He says, I promise.  Jesco, I'm your buddy
I do not steal all the steaks
Hey, something going on here ain't right.
But the alien had stolen them,
I'm gonna go track that son of a bitch down
to find him  that eat my steaks and stole them without asking
I'm gonna butcher him up like one and fry his ass
I get out in the woods.  I'm for life
and I'm all I'm pissed off  because my steaks has gone.
I had to pay big money for as a dog.
Who's that son of a bitch
who got my goddamn steaks?
He looks back at me and that shit.
He said, Hey,
you look like  you really want to stick me.
Oh, I did.
Cause I can't eat you  unless I get you on the far and cook you
like that he jumps over in the weeds.
stay out and be carried out ain't nothing this hollow worth dying for us they ought to be carried out
No trespassing.
This is  my advice on how to please a woman.
Don't ever argue with him
because you won't have a chance get your word in.
And three times  a husband don't have a chance.
Sex, drugs and money.
That's all a woman lives for.
This station is a mind blowing.
And it takes you  from sadness to happiness.
And it's a guarantee  to blow your mind.
cause jessica feels your heart full of love, and a man full of joy
Because when you do see something that pretty you're walking off leaving
you will miss it.
But you won't forget him when he throws his hand back to you.
it is cool as hell man
it's like letting your horse out of the barn ain't there
you just hear the horse trotting
and it's me.
You never conform.
Rebel Radio.
when you got the shits down here
in these part of the country's man
north,  south, west to east or west,
this is the best way to cure  your balance and get them unlocked
Go out
and get the biggest tree you can find if you can get your arms around and make sure you do
because you want to hold your hands on the other side
and take ten deep breaths and squeeze that tree
just as hard as you can.
Then let it out and I guarantee you
you'll shit  dislocate your newborn baby.
it's the best way to relieve you balance of in law.
He can't find the key.
叛逆电台
the home of gun control
progressive politics and break dancing
All of you radio listeners out there
horror of yet
needs of this to be a good deed and help  to drink more good whiskey
and you feel less pain.
And I guarantee you
you can dance and sing and be the happiest person on the planet.
It don't matter who you are.
Whatever you do is your business.
If it makes you happy, do it.
Well, turn it up on rebel radio.
We love you to death
because I was born to be war
as a rebel child without any calls.
And I'm drinking  whatever is in front of me.
cause she left the note on a door
You sleeping on the porch? You come home drunk one more time
Yes. And good country music going on.
And I guarantee  you going to love this station.
This is Rebel Radio, Bless your soul.
Wheel country
Rebel radio.
Well, my daddy told me one time,
he said, Son,  you got two heads,
one between your legs and one on your shoulders.
And one of them got a lack of sense.
And I said, You know why, Daddy?
he says well son
That’s because i'm living with two nuts
right around the  corner from an asshole.
Because country is go secede
Rebel radio
i huffed enough gas
filled my rocket ship three times power from the space shuttle
and a smoke more in the train
had hauls out to black gold
which keeps the lights on in my home
and food on the table
and shoes on my feet,
the code on my back.
And that's all I get to say,
because that's all I've got left.
I had a tumor
on the right side of my brain
and a blood clot on the left.
And I told the doctor
that I had appointment with.
He says,  There's not much we can do for you
that we can help you with.
He said,  because I tell you why,
going in on your brain is a dangerous operation.
It's a 50/50 chance you might stay and you might get to come back
I said, Well,
if you can‘t help me, Doctor,
why can't I be my doctor  and help myself
and smoke me a miracle
joint called the Miracle Pot Marijuana.
And I smoked that joint which held it in my lungs
and it took oxygen to my brain. Get the tumor, the munchies.
And he slides over on the left side
and needs to blood clot up
and then I get better.
We got this good contribution that we're already going out of here
because we're not stoned to the fact.
You all people think we're ripped out of frame, sound funny?
Give me a good rebel yell.
Hell, yeah.
Rebel radio
Hope y'all getting crazy out here
because I'm really getting fucked up
and ripped out of the frame.
I'm 20,000 years old,
so how could I be wrong?
Months a drunk assholes.
You're going to wake up and wonder what the fuck happened to you?
With rebel radio with Jesco
Now, how could I be right  if I'm wrong?
And this is Rebel radio.
I'm going to tell you what I'm going to put on my tombstone.
No more pussy alley.
No more whiskey I'll drink.
On your tombstone, you will read.
Here lies a legend
One of a kind with that rebel calls out of calls
land called Under the Dust.
I rob some grocery stores
I thought it was a thrill
because they had what I wanted.
I couldn't find it.  So I went in and took it.
And just to get high on, you know
what I'm saying  to get a buzz was lighter flooded
which was hooked on there like the gas, too.
So when the store was robbed,
they found the whole case lighter fluid going.
They know that I stole it cause
I took a whole case over
so I'd have enough to do me,
which was 24 cans
and not enough account a day
to get the full flick vouchers  I needed.
And that's how I become in trouble.
So i've done my time, learned from that not to do it again.
There ain't much of a squirrel,  but I'll tell you,
they're damn good eating.
And you can get one leg of the squirrels.  You got a bite,
which is really good. But the brain part of the squirrel
has better than a whole squirrel.
I call it soul  food for the hillbillies.
And you  can also take their town saddle as a roach clip
as you smoke Mary Jane.
This is Rebel Radio